When creating presentations, it's
always a good idea to plan out the
layout of the presentation before
you actually come to create it.
So as you can see, I have the content
on a Word document, which I wish
to transfer into the presentation.
This may be a document that's being
created by you, or it may be a
document that's been provided by
someone else in your organisation.
So as you can see, I need to transfer this
text, it's set out in such a way, so I'm
quite clear as to what needs to go where.
So I've got the title slide
which is slide one, slide two,
slide three and slide four.
And in this video, I'm just going
to quickly demonstrate how you
can add the text to the slides.
So as you can see, I've created a
new slide show and it automatically
starts with the slide one,
which will be the title slide.
So I need to copy the information
from the Word document and
place it into the presentation.
Now I'm going to copy the content for
the title slide so I can highlight
the text I want to copy and then
select the copy icon, or I can just
use the Control and C shortcut.
Once it's highlighted, go to the
presentation, click where I want to
paste it and select Control and V which
will paste the text into the slide.
I can then select the subheading for
that slide, again, Control and C,
place that into the subheading box,
Control and V, and that has added that.
At the moment, I'm not too concerned
with the format and the layout,
that's what, everything like
that will be dealt with later on.
So now I need to add slide two.
So if I go to slide two, new slide.
And I want a slide which
is a title and content.
And I will then copy the title
for slide two, paste it into
the title box on slide two.
And then the content for
slide two, I can copy that and
then place that into the box.
At the moment, as I say I'm not
too concerned, it's added a bullet
point, but I won't want that so
I will take that away later on.
And then again, another new slide
which is title and content, copy the
sub-heading or the heading, sorry.
And then the main body of text, add
that to the slide and then finally,
another new slide, title and content
copy and paste the heading for
that slide and then the content.
So there as you can see, I've now
added the content for all four of the
slides, so I am ready to start making
changes to the layout and the structure.